3분 후면 원자로가 폭발해
우린 이제 끝이야
"We've got 3 minutes till it blows.
We won't make it!"
어서 빠져나가세요
혼자라도 살아야죠
"You've got to get out of here!
Save yourself!"
"I won't leave you."
안 돼, 나만 갈 순 없어
"Don't worry about me.
I'm a robot. I'm just a machine!"
내 걱정은 말아요
난 로봇이라구요
한낱 쇠붙이에 불과해요
-"No, you're not. Not to me."
-Oh, my God.
그렇지 않아, 내게는
세상에
-What?
-I am extremely talented.
왜?
나 연기 너무 잘한다
그래, 아주 좋아
-Yeah. You're great.
-Yeah.
-Okay, let's take it from..
-No, I mean, I was really acting my ass off.
그럼 이제...
아냐, 방금은 정말
무아지경이었어
I thought I was pretty good, too.
나도 꽤 잘했는데
Yeah, you're solid. You're just no me.
너도 괜찮았지만
나랑은 차원이 다르다
You know what?
I think that's enough for now.
오늘은 이 정도만 하자
연습도 지나치면 해로워
I don't want to be over-rehearsed.
좋아
Fine. I'll do it without you!
나 혼자 할 거야
I don't need you or anybody else!
넌 필요 없어, 다 가버려
I'm gonna make it on my own!
혼자 해내고 말겠어!
You'll see! You'll all see!
두고 보라고!
다들 두고 봐!
The One With Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
So what are you auditioning for?
이번엔 무슨 오디션이야?
새 TV쇼거든
It's a new TV show.
I'm up for the part of Mac,
Machiavelli, or "Mac"!
맥 마키아벨리 역인데
일명 '맥'으로 통하지
난 로봇 파트너의 도움으로
범죄를 해결하는 탐정이고
I'm a detective and I solve crimes
with my robot partner.
그 로봇은 컴퓨터 휴머노이드
일렉트로닉 비밀 집행자인데
He's a computerized humanoid...
electronically enhanced
secret enforcer.
Or "C.H.E.E.S.E."
줄여서 '치즈'라고 하지
-So Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.?
-That's the title!
그럼 맥과 치즈네?
그게 바로 제목이야
이니셜 조합이 '치즈'라니
운 좋았지
They lucked out
that the initials spell "cheese."
That is lucky.
진짜 운 좋았다
So Joey, if you get this,
you're gonna be, like...
조이, 이번 일만 잘 풀리면
TV쇼 주인공이 되겠구나
the star of your own TV show.
I mean, you'll be like the "Big Cheese"
or the "Big Mac." Hey, you love those!
다시 말하면 '빅 치즈'
'빅 맥'도 괜찮다
다 네가 좋아하는 거잖아
Don't get your hopes up.
It probably won't happen.
너무 기대하지 마
가능성은 희박하니까
그런 말하는 거 아냐
Why would you say that?
너희들도 알잖아
TV쇼 주연이라니
Well, I mean, come on, guys.
My own TV show?
내게는 과분해
-I don't know if I'm good enough.
-I am.
난 아닌데
What are you talking about?
You're a terrific actor.
조이, 무슨 소리야
넌 훌륭한 배우야
-You really think so?
-How can you even ask that question?
정말 그렇게 생각해?
두말하면 잔소리지
오, 예쁘다
-She's pretty.
-Yeah. And she's really nice too.
그래
게다가 얼마나 상냥한데
She taught me all about
how to work with cameras...
나한테 이것저것 가르쳐줬어
방귀 냄새 맡는 연기며...
and "smell the fart" acting.
-I'm sorry. What?
-Excuse me?
저기...
- 뭐?
- 뭐라고?
짧은 시간에 많은 대사를 외우다
보면 가끔 까먹을 때가 있거든
It's like you got so many lines
to learn so fast...
sometimes you need time
to remember your next one.
So while you're thinking of it, you
take this pause where you look intense.
다음 대사를 생각하는 동안
심각한 표정을 짓는 거야
You know, like this:
봐, 이렇게
그렇구나
Okay.
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
이제 나온다
Mrs. Wallace? I'm Dr. Drake Ramorey,
your sister's surgeon.
윌러스 부인?
동생분의 신경외과 주치의
드레이크 라모레입니다
You sister is suffering from a...
동생분의 병명은...
Well, Eva, we've done
some excellent work here.
좋아요, 에바
오늘 대단한 성과가 있었소
And I would have to say
your problem is quite clear.
내가 단언하건데
당신의 문제는 명백합니다
All you want is a tinkle
그대의 소원은 서서 쉬하기
길쭉한 뭔가가 부러워
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
서서 쉬하고, 갖고 놀고
그냥 달려만 있어도 좋아
Or play with or simply let hang
I play Al Pacino's butt.
알 파치노의 엉덩이 역을 맡았다
All right?
알았어?
그 사람이 샤워하는 장면에서
내 엉덩이가 나오는 거야
He goes into the shower and then,
I'm his butt.
-Oh, my God.
-Come on, you guys.
망측해라
왜 이래
This is a movie and Al Pacino's in it,
and that's big!
알 파치노가 나오는 영화면
진짜 대단한 거야
그래, 잘됐다
It's terrific. You deserve this.
After years of struggling...
고생 끝에 드디어 영화판에
엉덩이 붙일 자릴 찾은 거야
you've finally cracked your way
into show business.
그래, 맘껏 놀려라
난 상관없어
Okay, fine, make jokes. I don't care.
This is a big break for me.
어쨌든 일생일대의 기회야
그럼, 맞는 말이야
-No, you're right, it is.
-Yeah.
그래
엉덩이 개봉하는 날
우리 초대할 거지?
So, you gonna invite us
to the big opening?
All right, I'm out of here. Wish me luck.
그럼 다녀올게
행운을 빌어줘
행운을 빌어요
우리 모두 행운을 빌어요
Good luck, good luck
We all wish you good luck
Yeah, whatever.
어쨌든 고맙다
Wow, if I could dance,
I'd be a triple threat.
춤까지 곁들였으면
금상첨화였을 텐데
It's your turn.
네 차례야
Oh, are we playing this?
두고 있는 거였어?
- 나 왔다
- 그래, 오디션은?
How'd the audition go?
Terrible. I messed up every word.
I shouldn't even be an actor.
망했다
대사를 다 씹었어
난 배우도 아냐
Wait. Are you pretending it didn't
go well, but it really did go well?
잠깐, 이건 또 잘됐는데
망친 척하는 그 연기겠지?
-Yeah, did I fool you?
-Totally!
맞아, 속았냐?
아무렴
-So it did go well?
-Amazingly well!
그럼 잘됐구나
기가 막히게 풀리더라
- 다행이다
- 축하해
-Great!
-It's down to me and two other guys.
나까지 해서 세 명으로 좁혀졌어
잘됐다
둘 다 아는 친구들인데
만만치가 않아
And they're really good.
One's from those allergy commercials
who's chased by flowers.
한 명은 알레르기 약 광고에서
커다란 꽃한테 쫓기는 남자야
Oh, I love that guy!
그 친구 맘에 들던데
What are you doing?
너 뭐하냐?
What am I doing?
내가 뭐하는 거지?
I'm so nervous, you know?
The callback is tomorrow at 5:00.
너무 떨린다
2차 오디션은 내일 5시야
머리가 터질 것 같아
-I feel like my head's gonna explode.
-Well, it is overdue.
그럴 때도 됐다
-Don't worry. You'll be fine.
-But it's so much pressure.
걱정 마, 잘될 거야
보통 스트레스가 아냐
What you guys do is different.
I don't know if you'd understand.
너희는 하는 일이 달라서
이런 기분 이해 못할 거야
그래, 우린 직장에서
스트레스 안 받지
Yeah, we don't have pressure
at our jobs.
I know what time it is, but I'm looking
at the wee-ness and I'm not happy.
그래, 몇 시인지는 나도 알아
날밤 까면 자기는 좋겠어?
Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
지금 상추 뜯고 있어요
더러운가요?
-Is it dirty?
-Don't worry, I'll wash it.
걱정 마세요, 씻을게요
아니에요
난 더러운 게 좋으니까
Don't. I like it dirty.
That's your call.
원하신다면 그렇게 해드리죠
그럼 다음은 뭘 할 건가요?
So what are you going to do next?
토마토를 잘라야겠어요
I thought I'd cut up the tomatoes.
Are they firm?
그거 단단한가요?
-They're all right.
-You sure they haven't gone bad?
네, 괜찮아요
혹시 상하진 않았나요?
흐물흐물하진 않겠죠?
You sure they're not very, very bad?
아뇨, 괜찮아요
-No, really. They're okay.
-You gonna slice them real nice?
잘근잘근 썰 건가요?
Actually, I was gonna
do them julienne.
채썰기로 하려구요
I'm out of here.
그만 가겠어요
모니카, 나 그만둘 거야
I'm quitting. I just helped
an 81-year-old woman put on a thong...
81살 할머니 끈팬티 입는 거
도와줬는데 안 사고 가버렸어
and she didn't even buy it.
농담 아냐, 진짜 그만둘래
당장 사표 낼 거야
I'm quitting. That's it.
I'm talking to my boss right now.
그래, 그만 둘 거야
그만두고 말겠어
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
이 메시지 받으면 전화해
Bye. Call me when you
get this message.
무슨 일인데?
Well, what happened?
이 남자가 마사지를
잘 받다가 갑자기...
Well, he came in for a massage,
and everything was fine until...
세상에
Oh, my God.
그런데 손버릇은
아무것도 아니었어
And all of a sudden,
his hands weren't the problem anymore.
그니까...
-Was it?
-Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
보이스카우트
천막 쳐도 되겠더라
제 샌드위치를 드셨어요?
You ate my sandwich?
It was a mistake.
It could happen to anyone.
흔히 있을 수 있는 실수 아닌가
그럴까요?
Really?
진정하게
Now calm down.
Come look in my office.
Some of it may still be in the trash.
내 사무실 쓰레기통에
남은 게 있을 거야
뭐라구요?
-What?
-Well, it was quite large.
너무 커서...
대부분은 그냥 버렸지
I had to throw most of it away.
내 샌드위치를 버렸다구요?
You threw my sandwich away?
내 샌드위치!
My sandwich?
My sandwich!
It's just, I want this part so much.
이 역은 꼭 맡고 싶어
이번에 미끄러지면...
If I don't get this part, I'm never gonna eat
macaroni and cheese again.
다신 마카로니치즈 안 먹을래
아냐, 취소, 말도 안 돼
I didn't say that. That doesn't count.
그만해라, 내가 무슨
유럽으로 이사 갔냐?
Come on, guys.
It's not like I moved to Europe.
복도 건너편이잖아
I just moved across the hall.
And we would have you over all the time...
나도 우리 집에서
너희들 키우고 싶었어
if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
모니카 알레르기만 아니면
맞아, 너희들한텐
거짓말 못하겠다
You're right, I could never lie to you.
모니카는 너희들 싫어해
She hates you.
Should I get that?
전화 받아도 돼?
Hello? No, Joey's not here right now.
Can I take a message?
여보세요
조이는 지금 없는데요
전해드릴까요?
네, 오디션 시간이 5시에서
2시 30분으로 변경됐다구요?
Yeah, okay. So the audition's
been moved from 5:00 to 2:30?
알겠습니다, 그럼
Okay, great. Bye.
아직 옷 안 입었어?
-Aren't you dressed yet?
-Am I naked again?
내가 또 발가벗고 있니?
We're meeting my parents
in 15 minutes.
15분 후에 우리 부모님
만나기로 했잖아
저 녀석들이랑 얘기했어
I was just talking to the guys.
Look at them.
한번 봐
Is it okay if they come visit?
가끔 놀러오라고 하자
내 알레르기는 어쩌고
What about my allergies?
맞아
Right. Your allergies.
알레르기 있었지
All her. She hates you.
온몸으로 너희를 거부하네
그렇지!
Yes! All right.
좋았어
How cool would it be if you could watch
a life-size version of this?
이 게임을 실물 크기로
본다면 기가 막히겠지?
-I mean, how crazy would that be?
-As crazy as soccer?
환상적일 거야
그게 축구 아닐까?
여보세요
Hello?
What are you talking about?
The audition's at 5.
무슨 말씀이세요
오디션은 5시인데
그런 얘기 못 들었어요
Well, nobody told me.
Who'd you talk to?
누구랑 통화했죠?
Never mind.
됐습니다
You mean you didn't get it from this?
이게 그 내용인지 몰랐냐?
그 알레르기 녀석이
뽑혔단다, 고맙구나
-The allergy guy got the part. Thanks.
-Maybe we can fix it.
그 친구한테 커다란 꽃다발을
보내서 겁을 주는 게 어떨까
Maybe we can send him
some big flowers and scare him!
어떻게 이럴 수가 있냐
내 인생이 바뀔 기회였는데
How could you do this? This could've
turned my career around.
I messed up, okay?
I'm sorry. I really messed up.
내 실수야
정말 미안하다
내가 죽일 놈이야
넌 여기 살지도 않잖아
Why'd you answer my phone?
내 전화는 왜 받아
응답기도 있는데
-I have a machine!
-Which I bought for you.
내가 사준 거 말이지?
사용법도 내가 가르쳐줬고
Taught you how to use it.
You thought it was a copier.
넌 복사기인 줄 알았잖아
내가 할 수 있는 일이라면
뭐든 하겠지만
If there was anything I could do,
I'd do it.
누구든 한 번은 실수하잖아
Everybody's allowed
one mistake, right?
비디오도 있고 골프채도 있는데
하필 여성 퇴치용 팔찌가 뭐야
He could have gotten me a VCR
or golf clubs.
But no, he has to get me
the "Woman Repeller."
리버라체 박물관 개구멍으로
빠져나온 짜가를!
The eyesore from
the "Liberace House of Crap!"
-It's not that bad.
-Easy for you to say.
그 정도는 아니다
그렇겠지, 넌 이따위 불량품
차고 돌아다닐 일 없으니까
You don't have to sport a reject
from the "Mr. T" collection.
챈들러, 그만해
I pity the fool who puts on my jewelry!
I do! I do!
내 꼴이 처량하고 한심해서
눈물이 다 나온다
I pity the fool that...
어떤 멍청이가... 왔냐?
어제 너 기다리면서
캐시랑 얘기하다가
When you were late last night,
Kathy and I were talking and...
one thing led to another and....
어쩌다 보니까...
And what? Did you sleep with her?
어쩌다 뭐?
캐시랑 잤냐?
아니, 그냥 키스만 했어
-No! No, I just kissed her.
-What? That's even worse!
뭐? 그게 더 나빠
-How?
-I don't know! But it's the same!
- 그게 왜 더 나빠?
- 몰라, 그게 그거지
그래, 변명의 여지가 없다
넘어선 안 될 선을 넘은 거야
I have no excuses.
I was over the line.
선을 넘어? 넌 무지막지하게
그 선을 짓밟고 지나갔어
Over the line?
You're so far past the line
you can't even see it!
선이 아니라 점이었겠지
The line is a dot to you!
I'm not saying you should
magically forgive me.
쉽게 용서하긴 힘들겠지만
너도 완벽한 건 아냐
But you're not perfect.
You've made errors in judgment.
가끔 실수하잖아
Name one!
하나만 대봐
What happened?
이게 뭐야
Man! He promised
he wouldn't take the chairs!
미치겠네, 의자는
안 가져간다고 해놓고
How were you locked in?
And where the hell's all of our stuff?
대체 거기는 왜 들어갔어
우리 세간은 다 어디 가고
This guy came to look at the unit...
어떤 인간이 와선 어른 하나도
못 들어갈 장식장이라고 하잖아
and he didn't think
it was big enough to fit a man.
So you got in voluntarily?
그래서 제 발로 들어갔어?
I was trying to make a sale!
물건 팔아먹기가 쉽냐?
If I ever run into him again,
know what I'll do?
그 자식 걸리기만 해봐
내가 어떡할지 알아?
Bend over?
공중제비라도 넘을래?
There's Lori.
저기 로리 온다
Remember, no trading.
You get the pretty one, I get the mess.
좋아, 바꾸기 없기다
넌 예쁜 여자, 난 폭탄
- 안녕, 조이
- 어서 와
-Hi, Joey.
-Hey.
Well, well. Look what you brought.
어머나, 굉장한
물건을 데려왔네?
And what did you bring?
그쪽은 어떤 물건을 데려왔죠?
She's checking her coat.
걔는 코트 맡기고 있어요
Joey, I'm gonna go wash
the cab smell off my hands.
조이, 택시 냄새가 배서
손 좀 씻고 와야겠어
Will you get me a white Zinfandel
and a glass of red for Janice.
난 화이트 진판델
재니스는 레드 한 잔
Janice?
재니스?
재니스라고?
Oh, my God!
오 마이 갓
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
조이의 재단사가 날 희롱했어
What?
뭐?
No way. I've been going
to the guy for 12 years.
말도 안 돼, 난 그 집
12년째 단골이야
You said he'd do my inseam...
안쪽 솔기 본다고 하면서
내 다리를 쓸어 올리더니...
then he ran his hand up my leg
and then there was...
What?
그래서?
Cupping.
쥐었어
That's how they do pants!
바지 맞출 땐 원래 그래
로스, 네가 말 좀 해줘
그렇게 재는 거잖아
-Isn't that how a tailor measures?
-Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
그래, 맞아
감옥에선!
I said name one!
하나만 대랬잖아
-I can't believe I did this.
-Stop beating yourself up.
그런 실수를 하다니
나 바보 아냐?
자책은 그만해
People make mistakes.
These things happen.
실수는 누구나 하는 거잖아
There aren't any messages
you've forgotten to give me?
나한테 전해줄 메시지
까먹은 거 없어?
Apparently, you're not very good at it.
사실 그 방면엔 문제가 있지
-Do you think he'll forgive me?
-Of course.
조이가 날 용서해줄까?
물론이지, 스스로를
용서하는 게 더 중요해
The important thing
is that you forgive yourself.
-You know what, I kind of have.
-Already?
용서한 것 같아
벌써?
That was pretty bad what you did.
그렇게 심한 짓을 해놓고?
He will forgive you.
용서해줄 거야
I like to bring a pad with me when
I answer the phone, okay?
그래서 난 전화 받을 때
항상 메모지부터 챙기지
-You didn't see how mad he was.
-I'm sure he'll forgive you.
조이가 화내는 걸 못 봐서 그래
글쎄 용서할 거라니까
우리 다들 그러고 살잖아
We've all been there. You fight,
you make up. That's how it works.
싸우고 화해하고
다 그런 거 아냐?
우리 사이가 이렇게 된 건
한 사람 잘못이 아냐
It took two people to break up
this relationship!
Yeah! You and that copy girl...
그래, 너랑 그 복사집 아가씨
어젠 다 네 잘못이라고 했잖아
which yesterday you took
responsibility for!
그땐 무슨 뜻인지
모르고 한 말이야
I didn't know what I was taking
responsibility for.
편지 끝까지 못 읽었어
-I didn't finish the letter.
-What?
- 뭐?
- 잠들었어
-I fell asleep.
-You fell asleep?
잠이 들어?
It was 5:30 in the morning.
새벽 5시 반이었어
넌 무려 18장에 걸쳐
장황하게 휘갈겨놨고
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
Front and back!
앞뒤로 꽉꽉!
참, 그리고
And by the way?
Y-O-U, apostrophe R-E means, "you are."
그리고 YOU'RE는
YOU ARE란 뜻이야
Y-O-U-R means "your."
YOUR가 아니라고!
I can't believe I thought
of getting back together with you.
다시 합치겠다고 생각한 내가
미쳤지, 이젠 완전히 끝장이야
We are so over!
Fine by me!
동감이외다!
잘 들어, 이런 복이 아무한테나
생기는 줄 아나 본데 정신 차려!
And just so you know,
it's not that common...
it doesn't happen to every guy,
and it is a big deal!
I knew it!
그럴 줄 알았어
-You had no right to go out with him.
-That's ridiculous..
네가 뭔데 그 남자를 만나?
- 모니카, 이게 무슨...
- 내 뒤통수를 친 거야
-You sold me out!
-I did not!
- 누가 뒤통수를 쳐?
- 뒤통수 친 게 아니면 뭔데?
-You did! You sold me..
-Would you let me talk?
나도 말 좀 하자
Did you just flick me?
지금 날 쳤니?
Well, you wouldn't let me finish and..
네가 내 말을 가로막고...
그만해!
Stop it!
- 하지 마!
- 그만!
-Stop.
애들아, 이러지 마
-All right. No, let's not do this.
-No!
-Happy thoughts.
좋게 생각해
좋게 생각해라니까
-Happy thoughts.
-No!
Okay, now I'm gonna kick some ass!
너희들 진짜 죽어볼래?
All right. Now, I will let go
if you both stop.
좋아, 그만두겠다고
약속하면 놔주겠어
-Fine.
알았어
좋아
그래야지
There we go.
여기가 감옥이었다면
너흰 영락없이 내 깔치야
You know what? If we were in prison,
you guys would be my bitches.
어떠냐, 이 녀석아
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
내 옷을 숨겼어?
난 네 옷 전부 껴입었다
You hide my clothes?
I'm wearing everything you own.
환장하겠네
Oh, my God!
봐라, 난 챈들러야
Look at me, I'm Chandler!
Could I be wearing any more clothes?
이보다 더 입을 순 없겠지?
유격대에 들어갈까 했는데...
Maybe if I wasn't going commando.
이렇게 껴입으니까 무지 덥다
I tell you, it's hot with all this on.
I'd better not do any lunges.
그럼 이런 거 하면 안 되겠지?
Joey?
조이?
조이 스페셜 사왔다
피자 두 판
Got you the Joey special! Two pizzas!
조이?
여보세요?
Hello? Damn it!
젠장
네?
Hello?
조이는 지금 없는데요
대신 전해드리죠, 잘되면...
No, Joey's not here right now,
but I can take a message. I think.
He's still got a chance for the part?
That's great news!
그 배역 아직 기회가 있어요?
그거 정말 잘됐네요
Well, no, obviously not for the actor
who was mauled by his dog.
물론 자기 개한테 물린
배우한테는 안된 일이죠
That's great.
I'll give Joey the message.
알겠습니다, 그렇게 전하죠
감사합니다
그렇지
Yes!
좋아
Okay.
Mac...
맥 오디션
audition...
2시
at 2:00.
알레르기 배우
Allergy...
actor...
attacked.
공격당함
By dog...
꽃이 아니라
개한테
not...
flowers.
야
내가 남긴 메모 봤지?
-Tell me you got the message.
-What message?
메모라니?
The actor playing Mac couldn't do it.
They needed you at 2.
맥 역할 맡은 배우가 다쳤다고
너 2시까지 오랬단 말이야
뭐?
지금 6시야
What? It's 6:00!
봐, 저기 써놨잖아
Look! I wrote it on the board!
이거 써놓고 너 찾으려고
시내를 이 잡듯이 뒤졌어
I wrote it down,
then went looking for you!
로스네 집, 커피하우스
샌드위치 만드는 가게는 몽땅
I went to Ross's, the coffee house...
I went to any place
they make sandwiches!
내가 정말 미치겠다
-I can't believe this, Chandler!
-I'm sorry.
미안해, 나도 할말이 없다
-I don't know what to say!
-You might say congratulations!
이런 말은 어때?
'축하해'
메모 보고 오디션 가서
배역 따냈다
I saw the board, I went to the audition,
I got the part!
이게 재미있냐?
내가 얼마나 걱정했는데
Was that funny? I was worried.
-I'm sorry.
-That fake-out thing is just mean.
미안하다...
장난도 때를 가려서 쳐야지
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make you feel bad.
알았어, 기분 상했다면 미안해
괜찮아
Well, that's good.
기분 하나도 안 상했다
이게 웬 경사냐
Because you didn't!
And I'm incredibly happy for you!
That's mean!
너야말로 심하잖아
- 가슴이 철렁했다
- 이러다 밤새겠다
-You had me going!
-We could do this all day.
Yeah, you're right.
그건 그래
Let's talk about what a huge star
I'm gonna be.
쓸데없는 소리 말고
대스타 조이를 감상하셔
넌 이제 대스타야
You're gonna be huge!
I'm gonna hug you!
- 안아줄게
- 안아줘
-You hug me!
-All right.
그래
-Do we do this too much?
-I think so.
우리 너무 자주 이러지 않냐?
그런 것 같다
- 떨어져라
- 그래
-Yeah. Get off me.
-Yeah.
"C.H.E.E.S.E.,
I'm not leaving without you.
안 돼, 치즈
널 두고 갈 순 없어
Route your backup power source
through your CPU."
예비 전력을
중앙처리장치로 돌려봐
안 돼요, 회로가 타버렸어요
새까맣게 타버렸다구요!
"l can't! My circuits are fried!
They're fried, I tell you!"
"Then I'll carry you!"
그럼 내가 들고 가야겠다
"That'll be a neat trick..."
그것도 좋겠지!
죽고 싶으면 마음대로 해!
"when you're dead!"
You don't have to yell.
소리 지를 필요 없어
방금 폭발이 일어났잖아
귀에 이상이 생겼을 거라고
There was just an explosion.
My hearing would be impaired.
I thought you were great.
내가 보기엔 좋았어
이런 착각까지 들더라
'어? 로스 어디 갔지?'
For a minute, I was like,
"Where'd Ross go?"
Thank you. And that first scene
where you meet Mac...
고마워, 네가 맥을
만나는 첫 장면 있지?
-Yeah?
-Oh, my God. I mean...
- 그래
- 죽였다, 알지?
And you know what?
됐어
That's enough for today.
Thanks for your help.
오늘은 그만하자
도와줘서 고맙다
-Holding us back.
-Totally.
위기감을 느끼겠지
아무렴